azerdict.com 2012-11-02

# AzerDict - Azerbaijani English Dictionary

**Website Visitors**

Like most websites, AzerDict collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, including: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform); and (d) the data in any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, which may include the word look-ups you previously submitted. AzerDict's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how AzerDict's visitors use its website. From time to time, AzerDict may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. AzerDict does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

**Data Collection and Protection**

AzerDict collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with AzerDict. AzerDict does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

AzerDict discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AzerDict's behalf or to provide services and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. AzerDict will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AzerDict discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when AzerDict believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AzerDict, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an AzerDict website and have supplied your email address, AzerDict may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with AzerDict and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 

AzerDict takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. AzerDict may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.

**Subscriptions**

If you choose to subscribe to word of the day, we will request just your e-mail address. If you are receiving Word of the Day email from us and wish to stop, simply use the "unsubscribe" link below the content of the email you received.

**Third Party Advertisers**

AzerDict uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). If you want to check the advertisement company's privacy policy too, please visit [google.com](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AzerDict uses cookies to help AzerDict identify and track visitors, their usage of AzerDict website, and their website access preferences. AzerDict visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AzerDict's websites, with the drawback that certain features of AzerDict's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AzerDict may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AzerDict's sole discretion. AzerDict encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

**Contact Information**

Our contact information is available at [Contact page](http://azerdict.com/contact/)
